Register of the Sino-Judaic Institute records
Hoover Institution Archives
- 2013 Incremental Materials, 1964-2012 (Box 10-32)
  - Correspondence, 1964-2007
    - Escroignard, Victor, 1989 (Box-folder 15: 33)
    - Etzion, Eran, undated (Box-folder 15: 34)
    - Exhibits in Munich, 1990s (Box-folder 15: 35)
    - Fairbank Center News, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 36)
    - Falter, Michael, 1995 (Box-folder 15: 37)
    - Fan Yuchen, 1995 (Box-folder 15: 38)
    - Fehl, Marina Reina, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 39)
    - Fei Chengkang, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 40)
    - Fendelman, Jill S., 1991 (Box-folder 15: 41)
    - Fern, William, 2007 (Box-folder 15: 42)
    - Films and video on the Jews in China, 1997 (Box-folder 15: 43)
    - Film documentation, 2005 (Box 15-16)
      - Martane, Anais, 2005 (Box-folder 15: 44)
      - Chen Yifei, 1997 (Box-folder 15: 45)
      - Kaifeng movie, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 46)
      - Glazer, Julie, undated (Box-folder 15: 47)
      - Grossman, Joan, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 15: 48)
      - Levaco, Ronald, 1996 (Box-folder 15: 49)
      - Nicols, Eran P., 1995 (Box-folder 15: 50)
      - Nulman, Andy, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 51)
      - Schwartz, Gary, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 52)
      - Schwarzacher, Lukas, undated (Box-folder 15: 53)
      - Shanghai ghetto, 2002 (Box-folder 15: 54)
      - Shanghai science, 1993 (Box-folder 15: 55)
      - Shopowitz, Karen, 1994 (Box-folder 15: 56)
      - Spunt, Georges, 2003 (Box-folder 15: 57)
      - Zodiac, 1997 (Box-folder 15: 58)
    - Fine, Wendy, 1992 (Box-folder 16: 1)
    - Fishman, Devora, 1996 (Box-folder 16: 2)
    - Fishman, Lillian, 1996 (Box-folder 16: 3)
    - Fleming, Peter, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 4)
    - Forward, 1992 (Box-folder 16: 5)
    - Foss, Ted, 1997 (Box-folder 16: 6)
    - Fox, Martin, 1989 (Box-folder 16: 7)
    - Frank, Linda, 1990s (Box-folder 16: 8)
    - Frankel, Raymond, 1991 (Box-folder 16: 9)
    - Frankfurter Runelschan Kaifeng, undated (Box-folder 16: 10)
    - Freund, Michael, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 16: 11)
    - Frey, Mark, 1993 (Box-folder 16: 12)
    - Friedman, Ed, undated (Box-folder 16: 13)
    - Friend, Beverly, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 16: 14)
    - Gaber, George, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 15)
    - Gabow, Leo, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 16: 16-18)
    - Gabow, Leo, articles and translation, 1980s (Box-folder 16: 19)
    - Galoob, Alice, 2003 (Box-folder 16: 20)
    - Gao Wangzhi, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 16: 21)
    - Gach, Gary, 1989 (Box-folder 16: 22)
    - Geneological inquiries, 1994 (Box-folder 16: 23)
    - German files, 1998 (Box-folder 16: 24)
    - Gidwitz, Betsy, 1982 (Box-folder 16: 25)
    - Gilberg, Arnold, 1994 (Box-folder 16: 26)
    - Gladney, Dru, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 27)
    - Glass, Irvine I., 1990-1992 (Box-folder 16: 28)
    - Gluck, Sidney, 1996 (Box-folder 16: 29)
    - Gluckman, Ron, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 16: 30)
    - Goldman, Rene, 1995 (Box-folder 16: 31)
    - Goldstein, Jonathan, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 17: 1)
    - Gong Fangzhen, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 17: 2)
    - Green, Judith, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 3)
    - Greenspan, Don, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 4)
    - Gross, Miriam, 1995 (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - Grossman, Gregory, 2005 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    - Grunfeld, Tom, 1989 (Box-folder 17: 7)
    - Gu Xiaoming, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 17: 8)
    - Pan Guang, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 17: 9)
    - Guide in China, Honey Kessler Amado, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 10)
    - Gurman, Tzierel, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 17: 11)
    - Hadassah Magazine, 1998 (Box-folder 17: 12)
    - Haggada reprint, Arthur Rosen, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 17: 13)
    - Hahn, Reinhard F., 1989 (Box-folder 17: 14)
    - Hakol, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 15)
    - Halle, Rolf von, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 16)
    - Hallo, Ruth, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 17: 17)
    - Handler, Frank, 1994 (Box-folder 17: 18)
    - Hanin, Leo, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 17: 19)
    - Harbin, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 17: 20)
    - Harbin Center for Judaic Studies, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 21)
    - Harvard conference list, 1997 (Box-folder 17: 22)
    - Hatefutsoth, Beth, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 17: 23)
    - Hebrew Union College, 1997 (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - Hebrew University Archives, undated (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - Henan University, undated (Box-folder 18: 3)
    - Heppner, Ernest, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 18: 4)
    - Hew, Len, 2003 (Box-folder 18: 5)
    - Hiroshima Memorial Project, 1994 (Box-folder 18: 6)
    - Hirshon, Jonathan, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 18: 7)
    - Ho Feng Shan, 2000 (Box-folder 18: 8)
    - Hochstadt, Steve, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 18: 9)
    - Holland - Amsterdam Jewish Museum, 2004 (Box-folder 18: 10)
    - Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 18: 11)
    - Holocaust Oral Project, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 18: 12)
    - Hongkew Chronicle, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 18: 13)
    - Hong Kong, 1997 (Box-folder 18: 14)
    - Hong Kong Society, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 18: 15)
    - Hoover Institution, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 18: 16)
    - Horal, Phyllis, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 18: 17)
    - Horowitz, Rose, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 18)
    - Hoxmeier, Dianne J., 1994 (Box-folder 18: 19)
    - Hua Kuang Chinese Reading Room, 1992 (Box-folder 18: 20)
    - Igud Yotzei Sin, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 18: 21)
    - India, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 18: 22)
    - Institute for Chinese-Western Cultural History, undated (Box-folder 18: 23)
    - Institute for World Religions, 1991 (Box-folder 18: 24)
    - Internet - website domain, 2003 (Box-folder 18: 25)
    - International Center for University Teaching of Jewish Civilization, 1995 (Box-folder 18: 26)
    - Israel, 1993 (Box-folder 18: 27)
    - Israel, Chinese Jews in, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 1)
    - Israel China Treaty, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 2)
    - Israel Embassy in Beijing - Eyal Propper, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 3)
    - Israeli Consulate, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 19: 4)
    - Israeli, Raphael, speaking engagement flyer, undated (Box-folder 19: 5)
    - Jacob's voyage, 1997 (Box-folder 19: 6)
    - James, S. E., 1991 (Box-folder 19: 7)
    - Japan, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 19: 8)
    - Jerusalem Letter, 1985 (Box-folder 19: 9)
    - Jerusalem Post, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 10)
    - Jewish communities clippings, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 11)
    - Jewish Community Federation, 1990 (Box-folder 19: 12)
    - Jewish Film Festival, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 13)
    - Jewish History Research Center of Shanghai, 1989 (Box-folder 19: 14)
    - Jewish Historical Tours of China, undated (Box-folder 19: 15)
    - Jewish Museum, New York, undated (Box-folder 19: 16)
    - Jewish National and University Library, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 19: 17)
    - Jewish Publication Society, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 18)
    - Jewish terminology, 2005 (Box-folder 19: 19)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 1994 (Box-folder 19: 20)
    - Jin Jiang Tours, 1990 (Box-folder 19: 21)
    - Gu Junjie, 1991 (Box-folder 19: 22)
    - Jin Xiaojing, "I Am a Chinese Jew,", undated (Box-folder 19: 23)
    - Johnston, Tess, 1990-2002 (Box-folder 19: 24)
    - Josephson, Marvin, 1995 (Box-folder 19: 25)
    - Judaism bibliography, undated (Box-folder 19: 26)
    - Kahn, Michele, 1990s (Box-folder 19: 27)
    - Kaifeng, 1986-2007 (Box-folder 19: 28-29)
    - Kaifeng clippings, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 19: 30)
    - Kaifeng documentary, 1998 (Box-folder 19: 31)
      Includes correspondence regarding the documentary, "Minyan in Kaifeng."
    - Kaifeng, Jewish question, 1998 (Box-folder 19: 32)
    - Kaifeng material, 1982-2005 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - Kaifeng, Moshe Zhan, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 20: 2)
    - Kaifeng Museum, undated (Box-folder 20: 3)
    - Kaifeng project, 2003 (Box-folder 20: 4)
    - Kaifeng talk notes, undated (Box-folder 20: 5)
    - Kaplan, Fred, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 20: 6)
    - Kaplan, Norman, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 20: 7)
    - Kaplan, Roy, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 8)
    - Kaplan, Seth - Shanghai, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Katz, Professor Nathan, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 20: 10)
    - Katz, Theodore, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 11)
    - Kaufman, Alex, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 12)
    - Kaufman, Isai, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 13)
    - Kaufman, Joseph, 1997 (Box-folder 20: 14)
    - Kawashima, Kazue, 2001 (Box-folder 20: 15)
    - Kaye, Ronald L., 1980-1991 (Box-folder 20: 16)
    - Kipen, Israel, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 17)
    - Knapp, Alexander, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 20: 18)
    - Kogan, Mary, 1995 (Box-folder 20: 19)
    - Kogan, Sheila L., 1993-1994 (Box-folder 20: 20)
    - Kolman, Patricia, undated (Box-folder 20: 21)
    - Koret Foundation, undated (Box-folder 20: 22)
    - Kramer, Larry, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 23)
    - Kranzler, David, clipping, 1979 (Box-folder 20: 24)
    - Krasno, Rena, 1990-2006 (Box-folder 20: 25)
    - Kulano, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 20: 26)
    - Kutner, Philip, 1994 (Box-folder 20: 27)
    - Laytner, Anson, 1990 (Box-folder 20: 28)
    - Lehmann, Manfred R., 1992 (Box-folder 20: 29)
    - Leibler, Isi, 1992 (Box-folder 20: 30)
    - Leiden, Rijks Universitait, 1994 (Box-folder 20: 31)
    - Lengyel, Alfonz, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 20: 32)
    - Leningrad library book exchange, 1994 (Box-folder 20: 33)
    - Leo Baech Institute, 1983 (Box-folder 20: 34)
    - Leslie, Donald, 1999 (Box-folder 20: 35)
    - Levaco, Ben, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - Leve, Harvey A., 1992 (Box-folder 21: 2)
    - Leventhal report, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - Leventhal, Dennis, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 21: 4-5)
    - Levin, Burton - The Asia Society Hong Kong Center, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 21: 6)
    - Levine, Hillel, 1994 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - Levy, Daniel, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - Levy, Mary, 2004 (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - Li Jingwei, 1990 (Box-folder 21: 10)
    - Li Runtian, Henan University, 1986 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - Li Wei, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 21: 12)
    - Liaison Office, 1990 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - Lin Meicun, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 14)
    - Lincoln, Trebitsch, 1988 (Box-folder 21: 15)
    - Ling Jie, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 16)
    - Lippmann, David, 1993 (Box-folder 21: 17)
    - Littauer Foundation, 2004 (Box-folder 21: 18)
    - Liu Don, 1996 (Box-folder 21: 19)
    - Liu Feng, Kaipeng delegation, 1990 (Box-folder 21: 20)
    - Liu Wenqing, 1990 (Box-folder 21: 21)
    - Liu Wushu, 1994 (Box-folder 21: 22)
    - Liu Xianzhi, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 23)
    - Loewenthal papers location, 2003 (Box-folder 21: 24)
    - Lost Tribes clipping, 1991 (Box-folder 21: 25)
    - Low, Ed, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 21: 26)
    - Lowy, Robert, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    - Lu Fan, Shandong University, Centre for Judaic and Inter-Religious Studies, 1994-2006 (Box-folder 21: 28)
    - Lubowich, Kenneth, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 21: 29)
    - Lui Yaozhong, undated (Box-folder 21: 30)
    - Lu Changlin, 1997 (Box-folder 21: 31)
    - Luk, Alfred, 1995 (Box-folder 21: 32)
    - Lurie, Jane, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 33)
    - Magnes Museum, 1998 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Mailings, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 2)
    - Father Malatesta, 1998 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - Malkin, Leslie, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - Malloy, Ruth, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - Maori and Jewish cultures, 1997 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - Marcus, Audrey, 2006 (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - Marcus, Herbert, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - Matthews, Morris, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - Mayer, Robert, 1998 (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - Meeting space at the Los Altos Library, undated (Box-folder 22: 11)
    - Members' information, undated (Box-folder 22: 12)
    - Meng, Weiyan, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - Messmer, Mattias, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 22: 14)
    - Meyer, Maisie, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - Meyerson, Morton, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - Meyerstein, Ralph, 1994 (Box-folder 22: 17)
    - Miao, Kitty, 1992 (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - Miller, David, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22: 19)
    - Miller, Marcia, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 22: 20)
    - Mongolia - Morris Rossabi, 2003 (Box-folder 22: 21)
    - Monumenta Serica, 1996 (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - Moshe Leah Scrolls, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 22: 23)
    - Moskow, Shirley, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22: 24)
    - Moustafine, Mara, 1990s (Box-folder 22: 25)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 26)
    - National Public Radio, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 27)
    - National Yiddish Book Center, 1991 (Box-folder 22: 28)
    - Needle, Dr. M. Patricia, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 22: 29)
    - Nelson, Ethel R., 1994 (Box-folder 22: 30)
    - New Voices, 2001 (Box-folder 22: 31)
    - Nissim, Matook, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 22: 32)
    - Nobler, Milton G., 1990-1992 (Box-folder 22: 33)
    - November, Tsvi Harvey, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 34)
    - Nulman, Andrew, 1995 (Box-folder 22: 35)
    - Ochert, Morris S., 1992-1997 (Box-folder 22: 36)
    - Odens, Peter R., 1991 (Box-folder 22: 37)
    - Ohel Moshe, 2007 (Box-folder 22: 38)
    - Onorato, Michael P., 1991 (Box-folder 22: 39)
    - Oral history project, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 40)
    - Organizations dealing with China, undated (Box-folder 22: 41)
    - Oxbridge listing, 1991 (Box-folder 22: 42)
    - Pacific Jewish Theatre, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 43)
    - Pan, George, 1992-2005 (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - People's Republic of China contacts, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - Petruck, Miriam R. L., 1996 (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - Phillips, Eleanor, 1991 (Box-folder 23: 4)
    - Piastunovich, Teddy, 2003 (Box-folder 23: 5)
    - Pinto, D., 1994 (Box-folder 23: 6)
    - Piver, David E., 1994 (Box-folder 23: 7)
    - Plaks, Andrew, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 23: 8)
    - Platek, Todd L., 1997 (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - Pluss, Caroline B., 1999 (Box-folder 23: 10)
    - Points East, 1991-2004 (Box-folder 23: 11)
    - Pollack, Curt M., 1993 (Box-folder 23: 12)
    - Pollack, Michael, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 23: 13-14)
    - Pollack, Michael, digitizing Torah project, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 15)
    - Press releases, 1991 (Box-folder 23: 16)
    - Pritzker, Kenneth P. H., 1996 (Box-folder 23: 17)
    - Publications and publishers, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 23: 18)
    - Quill Corporation, 1991-2004 (Box-folder 23: 19)
    - Wang Qingyu, 1993 (Box-folder 23: 20)
    - Diane Rabinowitz, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 23: 21)
    - Raddock, David M., 1990 (Box-folder 23: 22)
    - Radio program, 1997 (Box-folder 23: 23)
    - Radom, Janna, 1994 (Box-folder 23: 24)
    - Raiklen, Harold, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 25)
    - Rauch, John H., Center for Jewish Culture and Creativity, 1999 (Box-folder 23: 26)
    - Ravel, Uri, 1990 (Box-folder 23: 27)
    - Religion in China clippings, 1994 (Box-folder 23: 28)
    - Reprint Greenwood Press, 1989 (Box-folder 23: 29)
    - Reprint project, 1988 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Resource magazine, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - Ricci Institute, 1990s (Box-folder 24: 3)
    - Rice, Mark, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - Richardson, Edgar, undated (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - Ristaino, Marcia, 1993-2006 (Box-folder 24: 6)
    - Rittenberg, Sidney, clipping, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 7)
    - Roland, Joan, 1996 (Box-folder 24: 8)
    - Rosen, Art, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 24: 9)
    - Rosen, Linda, 1992 (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - Rosenson, Hyman, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 24: 11)
    - Rotstein, Gena, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 24: 12)
    - Rutstein, Harry, 1990s (Box-folder 24: 13)
    - Russia, 1988 (Box-folder 24: 14)
    - Sabbath, Mildred, undated (Box-folder 24: 15)
    - Safadi, Michael, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 16)
    - Saidel, Rochelle, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 24: 17)
    - Sakamoto, Pam, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 18)
    - Salzburg meeting, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 19)
    - Sandberg, Niel C., 1990-2002 (Box-folder 24: 20)
    - San Francisco refugees, 1991 (Box-folder 24: 21)
      Rabbi Theodore Alexander, B'nai Amoona Synagogue.
    - Sardis Synagogue, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 24: 22)
    - Sasoon, Phillip, 1999 (Box-folder 24: 23)
    - Sassoon International Center for the Study of Anti-Semitism, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 24)
    - Schmidt, Beth, undated (Box-folder 24: 25)
    - Schneier, Arthur, 1998 (Box-folder 24: 26)
    - Schocken Books, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 27)
    - Schorsch, Ishman, Jewish Theological Seminary, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 28)
    - Schuman, Dean, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 29)
    - Schwartz, Jefferey, 1998 (Box-folder 24: 30)
    - Schwartz, Louis, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 24: 31)
    - Schwarcz, Vera, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 24: 32)
    - Seidel, Anna, 1989 (Box-folder 24: 33)
    - Seltzer, Leon, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 34)
    - Sender, Harry, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 35)
    - Sephardic community, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 24: 36)
    - Shan Fuliang, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 37)
    - Shanghai Jewish Center, 1992 (Box-folder 24: 38)
    - "Jewish Relics in Shanghai," by Gao Wangshi, 1988 (Box-folder 24: 39)
    - Shanghai maps of Jewish sites materials, 1991 (Box-folder 24: 40)
      Includes maps, correspondence, and notes.
    - Shillong, Ben-Ami, 1990 (Box-folder 24: 41)
    - Site inquiries, Jewish, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 42)
    - E. Spunt films, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - Spunt, Georges C., 1996 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - Sqadron, Howard M., 1992 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - Stampfer, Rabbi Joshua, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 25: 4)
    - Starkman, Betty, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 25: 5)
    - Starr, Nathan, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 6)
    - Stone, Paul, 1993 (Box-folder 25: 7)
    - Strelow, Monica, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 25: 8)
    - Sugihara, Chiune, 1994 (Box-folder 25: 9)
    - Xiao Xian, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 25: 10)
    - Kong Xiani, 1986 (Box-folder 25: 11)
    - Li Xiaojie, undated (Box-folder 25: 12)
    - Xu Xin, proposals, 2000 (Box-folder 25: 13)
    - Xu Boyong, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 14)
    - Xu Buzeng, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 25: 15)
    - Wang Yisha, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 16)
    - Yu Cheng, 1991 (Box-folder 25: 17)
    - Zafren, Herbert C., 1989 (Box-folder 25: 18)
    - Zhang Qianhong, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 25: 19)
    - Zhao stele, 1990 (Box-folder 25: 20)
  - Institutional records and correspondence, 1982-2007
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Accomplishments, 1992 (Box-folder 25: 21)
    - Article exchanges, 2000 (Box-folder 25: 22)
    - Association for Jewish Studies, 2002 (Box-folder 25: 23)
    - Baghdadi Jews, 2002 (Box-folder 25: 24)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 25)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 26: 1-10)
    - Board meeting minutes, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 27: 1-6)
    - Board member list, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Board member memorandum, 2002 (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - Book project, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 27: 9)
    - Business cards, undated (Box-folder 27: 10)
    - Bylaws, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 27: 11)
    - Chengdu building, 2002 (Box-folder 27: 12)
    - Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 27: 13)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 27: 14)
    - DNA project, 2000 (Box-folder 27: 15)
    - Election correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 27: 16)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1986 (Box-folder 27: 17)
    - Financial reports, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - Floppy disk, "Jewish Community of Singapore Cohesion, Dispersion, Survival,", 2002 (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - Founding documents and bylaws, 1985 (Box-folder 28: 3)
    - Gilman Conference, 2002 (Box-folder 28: 4)
    - Jonathan Goldstein grant, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - Guides to Shanghai, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 28: 6)
    - Haggadah, undated (Box-folder 28: 7)
      Multi-lingual Jewish Passover text.
    - Hannukah letter, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 28: 8)
    - Harbin cemetery, 2000 (Box-folder 28: 9)
    - Historical material, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 28: 10)
    - Holocaust Memorial Museum holdings, 1993 (Box-folder 28: 11)
    - Hong Kong, 2000 (Box-folder 28: 12)
    - Igud Yotzei Sin archive, 2002 (Box-folder 28: 13)
    - Inquiries, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 28: 14)
    - Institute correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 28: 15-17)
    - Institute correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 29: 1-6)
    - Institute correspondence, historical, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - Institute history, 1989 (Box-folder 29: 8)
    - Institute taxes, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 29: 9)
    - Inventory, 1999 (Box-folder 29: 10)
    - IRS correspondence, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 29: 11)
    - Jewish life in Beijing, 1996 (Box-folder 29: 12)
    - Jewish merchants, 1994 (Box-folder 29: 13)
    - Jewish Studies Bulletin, 2006 (Box-folder 29: 14)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 2002 (Box-folder 29: 15)
    - Kaifeng, 2000 (Box-folder 29: 16)
    - Kaifeng Center, 2002 (Box-folder 29: 17)
    - Kaifeng hospital project, 2000 (Box-folder 29: 18)
    - Kaifeng Jesuits, undated (Box-folder 29: 19)
    - "Kaifeng Jews in China" materials, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 29: 20)
    - Kaifeng Jews slide presentation, undated (Box-folder 29: 21)
    - Membership directory, 1995 (Box-folder 29: 22)
    - Membership report, 2000 (Box-folder 29: 23)
    - Mirsky, Jonathan, book review, 2002 (Box-folder 29: 24)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Nanjing Center, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - Nanjing Center contributions, 2001 (Box-folder 30: 3)
    - "A Network of Archival Resources Proposal,", undated (Box-folder 30: 4)
    - New business, 2002 (Box-folder 30: 5)
    - Newspaper clipping, He Fengshan, 2000 (Box-folder 30: 6)
    - Northridge Archives, 2002 (Box-folder 30: 7)
    - Ohel Moshe Synagogue of Shanghai, correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - Ohel Rachel Synagogue of Shanghai, undated (Box-folder 30: 9)
    - Old business, 2000 (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - People's Republic of China namelist, 1993 (Box-folder 30: 11)
    - Pollack, Michael, archive, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 30: 12)
    - Points East error, 2002 (Box-folder 30: 13)
    - Preserving Tolerance grant letter, 2001 (Box-folder 30: 14)
    - Proposal by Boris Bresler, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 30: 15)
    - Proposal by Li Chengyuan, 2000 (Box-folder 30: 16)
    - Proposal draft, 2002 (Box-folder 30: 17)
    - Proposal by Seth Garz, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 30: 18)
    - Proposal by Xu Xin, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30: 19)
    - Questions, 2002 (Box-folder 30: 20)
    - Report on visit to China, Albert Dien, 1991 (Box-folder 30: 21)
    - Report to the Board of Directors, 1991 (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - Reunion, Old China Hands, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - Ross Foundation, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - Royal Ontario Museum, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 31: 4)
    - San Jose Mercury News, "The Jews of China," article regarding Kaifeng Jews by Michael McCabe, 1984 November 17 (Box-folder 31: 5)
    - Scriptorium update, 2000 (Box-folder 31: 6)
    - Shanghai bibliography project, 1997 (Box-folder 31: 7)
    - Shanghai China Update newsletter, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 8)
    - Shanghai community, 1997 (Box-folder 31: 9)
    - Shanghai slides, 1997 (Box-folder 31: 10)
    - Shi Lei Fund, 2001 (Box-folder 31: 11)
    - Silkroad magazine, "From Mao to Matzo: The Historic Jewish-Chinese Community of Kaifeng," article by Wendy Abraham, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 12)
    - Sino-Judaica, vol. 3, 2000 (Box-folder 31: 13)
    - Source materials dealing with Jews in China, undated (Box-folder 31: 14)
    - Sources of information on the Jewish refugees in China, undated (Box-folder 31: 15)
    - Stylesheet, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 16)
    - Symposium materials, 1994 (Box-folder 31: 17)
    - Tientsin map, undated (Box-folder 31: 18)
    - Tombstones correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 19)
    - "Translation of the 1512 Inscription,", undated (Box-folder 31: 20)
    - Wang Yixia, "New Trends and Achievements in the Research on the Ancient Chinese Jews,", undated (Box-folder 31: 21)
    - Website, 2000 (Box-folder 31: 22)
    - Youtai symposium, "Presence and Perception of Jews and Judaism in China,", 2002 (Box-folder 31: 23)
    - Zeiden media proposal for "Safe Haven in China: The Untold History of the Jews Documentary,", 2003 (Box-folder 31: 24)
  - Exhibit records, 1985-2003
    - Belzer, Annie, 2001 (Box-folder 31: 25)
    - Brochure, "The Jews of Kaifeng" traveling museum exhibit, 2000 (Box-folder 31: 26)